Watch Online Movies and Series for FREE
www.osdb.link/lm
(HORSE NEIGHING)
(MEN SHOUTING)
Pod.
Pod!
Find Bronn
or Varys.
Tell them I am here
with Maester Pycelle.
Tell them I am
very much alive.
Yes. my lord.
Would you like
something for the pain?
What happened?
The murderer
and traitor
Stannis Baratheon
suffered a stunning defeat
at the hands of your father.
Where am I?
These are your new chambers.
A little cramped. perhaps.
but you don't need
much room. do you?
You are no longer
Hand of the King.
For your trouble.
I. Joffrey of
the House Baratheon.
first of my name.
the rightful
King of the Andals
and the First Men.
Lord of the Seven Kingdoms
and Protector of the Realm.
do hereby
proclaim my grandfather.
Tywin Lannister.
the savior of the city
and the Hand of the King.
Thank you. Your Grace.
Lord Petyr Baelish.
step forward.
For your good
service and ingenuity
in uniting the Houses
of Lannister and Tyrell.
I declare that
you shall be granted
the castle of Harrenhal
with all its
attendant lands and incomes
to be held by
your sons and grandsons
from this day
until the end of time.
You honor me beyond words.
Your Grace.
I shall have to acquire
some sons and grandsons.
(CROWD LAUGHING)
Ser Loras Tyrell.
Your house has
come to our aid.
The whole realm
is in your debt.
none more so than I.
If your family would
ask anything of me.
ask it.
and it shall be yours.
Your Grace.
my sister Margaery.
her husband was
taken from us before...
She remains innocent.
I would ask you to
find it in your heart
to do us the great honor
of joining our houses.
Is this what you want.
Lady Margaery?
With all my heart.
Your Grace.
I have come to
love you from afar.
Tales of your
courage and wisdom
have never been
far from my ears.
And those tales
have taken root
deep inside of me.
I. too. have heard tales
of your beauty and grace.
but the tales do not
do you justice. my lady.
It would be an honor
to return your love.
but I am promised to another.
A king must
keep his word.
Your Grace.
in the judgment of
your Small Council.
it would be
neither proper nor wise
for you to wed
the daughter of a man
beheaded for treason.
a girl whose brother
is in open rebellion
against the throne
as we speak.
For the good of the realm.
your councilors beg you
to set Sansa Stark aside.
(CROWD MURMURING)
MAN: Margaery!
MAN 2: We want Margaery!
JOFFREY: I would like
to heed your wishes and
the wishes of my people.
but I took a holy vow.
PYCELLE: Your Grace.
the gods do indeed
hold betrothal solemn.
but your father.
blessed be his memory.
made this pact
before the Starks
revealed their falseness.
I have consulted
with the High Septon
and he assures me
that their crimes
against the realm
free you from any promise
you have made to them
in the sight of the gods.
The gods are good.
I am free to
heed my heart.
Ser Loras.
I will gladly wed
your sweet sister.
You will be my queen
and I will love you
from this day
until my last day.
(ALL APPLAUDING)
(CHUCKLES)
My lady.
(GASPS)
My sincerest condolences.
They're right.
I'm not good
enough for him.
You shouldn't say that.
You'll be good enough
for many things.
He'll still enjoy
beating you.
And now that
you're a woman.
he'll be able to enjoy you
in other ways as well.
But. if he's
not marrying me...
He'll let you go home?
Joffrey's not the sort of boy
who gives away his toys.
You have a tender heart.
just like your mother did
at your age.
I can see so much
of her in you.
She was like a sister to me.
For her sake.
I'll help get you home.
King's Landing is
my home now.
Look around you.
We're all liars here.
And every one of us
is better than you.
(KNOCKING ON DOOR)
Come in.
Make yourself comfortable.
That doesn't look
very comfortable.
Here. watch me.
No need for that. my dear.
You sure?
Most men like what they see.
I'm not like most men.
That's what most men say.
(LAUGHS)
If you don't want
what most men want.
then you'd better tell me
what you'd like me to do.
I would like you
to tell me if working
for Lord Baelish
has been all you'd
hoped it would be.
Have we met?
You wouldn't
remember me if we had?
I meet a lot of men.
And I think you
remember all of them.
I think your true talents
are wasted on them.
You're very kind. my lord.
Allow me to return the favor.
You're afraid.
Why? Nothing dangerous
down there.
I know who you are.
And. unlike
your current employer.
I protect those
who work for me.
I don't abuse them
to satisfy royal whims
or force them to
abuse each other.
How do you know about that?
I thought you said
you knew who I was.
What can I do for you.
Lord Varys?
Littlefinger looks at you
and sees a collection
of profitable holes.
I see
a potential partner.
I'm afraid of him.
Oh. you should be.
He's a dangerous man.
But everyone has
their weaknesses.
Your current employer
hides his very well.
but not as well
as he thinks.
You're a virgin.
I take it?
Walk.
Childhood must have
been awful for you.
Were you
a foot taller than
all the boys?
They laughed at you.
called you names?
Some boys
like a challenge.
One or two must have tried
to get inside Big Brienne.
One or two tried.
Ah.
But you fought
them off.
But maybe
you wished
one of them could
overpower you.
fling you down.
tear off your clothes.
But none of them
were strong enough.
I'm strong enough.
Not interested.
Of course you are.
You'd love to know
what it feels like
to be a woman.
JAIME: Ah.
"They lay with lions."
Tavern girls. I'd say.
Probably served
my father's soldiers.
Maybe one of them gave
up a kiss and a feel.
That's how they earned this.
The glorious work
of the Northern
freedom fighters.
Must make you proud
to serve the Starks.
I don't serve the Starks.
I serve Lady Catelyn.
Tell yourself that tonight
when they swing
in your dreams.
What are you doing?
Burying them.
We shouldn't stay here.
We should get
back on the river.
I think these women
would understand if...
I don't care
what you think.
MAN: I didn't leave it here.
I had me dagger.
Untie me. Now!
MAN: I gave it to
you to cut the rope.
and now I don't
have me dagger no more.
So unless it got
stuck in your arse
on its way to your cunt.
it stands to reason
that it's gone. Whoa.
What's your business here?
Traveling a prisoner.
(LAUGHS)
You're a woman.
A woman!
Well. fuck me!
If you've quite
finished up...
(LAUGHING CONTINUES)
All right.
we'll be going.
Whoa. Whoa!
Who do you fight for?
The Starks.
What did he do?
Apparently eating is
now a crime. Who knew?
No. stealing is a crime.
But it's not
a crime to starve.
That's justice for you.
Where are you taking him?
To Riverrun.
Why Riverrun?
Steal from the Tullys.
it's their dungeons
you rot in.
Why not kill him?
For stealing a pig?
I don't give the orders.
He must be
important to someone.
Sending him with you?
How important could he be?
All right.
have it your way.
my lady.
Do I know you?
Have you been
to Ashemark?
No.
Then you don't know me.
Do you ever go to
the river market
at Salt Rock?
Is it near Ashemark?
No.
I've never been there.
What do you think
of these beauties?
I hope you gave
them quick deaths.
Two of them
we did. yeah.
Wait.
I do know you.
That's Jaime Lannister.
I wish someone had told me.
I wouldn't have had
to steal that pig.
If this is the Kingslayer.
I think I'd know about it.
How do you know what
the Kingslayer looks like?
I was at Whispering Wood.
I saw him.
(CHUCKLES)
They dragged him
out of the woods
and threw him
down before the king.
He's not the Kingslayer.
Sorry to disappoint you.
If he was. I'd only
be traveling his head.
I have a question
for you both.
And I want you
to answer it
at the same time.
I count to three.
you both answer.
What's his name?
One.
Two. Three.
(GROANS)
(GRUNTS)
Two quick deaths.
(STABBING)
(GROANING)
(PANTING)
Those were Stark men.
I don't serve the Starks.
I serve Lady Catelyn.
I told you I'd take
you to King's Landing.
and that's what
I'm going to do.
Stay.
(GRUNTS)
Walder Frey is
a dangerous man to cross.
I know that.
And you mean to
do it anyway?
I love her.
I know that seems
important to you.
It is important to me.
Your father didn't
love me when we married.
He hardly knew me or I him.
Love didn't
just happen to us.
We built it
slowly over the years.
stone by stone.
for you. for your
brothers and sisters.
for all of us.
It's not as exciting
as secret passion
in the woods.
but it is stronger.
It lasts longer.
And that is what
would be in store for me
with one of
Walder Frey's daughters.
what you and father had?
Why not?
Because she's not beautiful?
Because she's not
exotic and exciting?
Now you're arguing
just to argue because
you arranged it.
And you agreed to it.
You gave him your word.
Treat your oaths
recklessly.
and your people
will do the same.
If your father lived
his life for one thing...
My father is dead.
And the only parent
I have left
has no right to
call anyone reckless.
(THUNDER RUMBLING)
You said you saw
my victory in the flames.
MELISANDRE: I did.
I still see it.
The flames lied.
And I'm no better
than a savage
trusting in a fire god.
I fought for your god
in Blackwater Bay.
I led my men to
the gates of
the seventh hell
as their brothers
burned alive. and for what?
Attacked from behind
by Tywin Lannister
and the Tyrells.
If you see so much
in your flames.
why didn't you warn me?
The Lord of Light
only allows me glimpses.
You claimed to
speak for a god.
Will you quit the war
just because
you've lost a battle?
You talk about war as
if you understand it.
I've been fighting
far longer than you.
Have you?
Show me how you fight.
(CHOKING)
Show me.
Where's your god now?
Will he save you?
Where is your god?
Inside you.
(EXHALES)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
I murdered my brother.
We murdered him.
Share the weight
with me.
He wasn't your brother.
This war
has just begun.
It will last
for years.
Thousands will die
at your command.
You will betray
the men serving you.
your family.
You will betray
everything you
once held dear.
And it will all
be worth it
because you are
the Son of Fire.
You are
the Warrior of Light.
You will sweep aside
this pretender
and that one.
You will be king.
You promise these things.
but you don't know.
None of us know.
Let me show you.
Look into the fire.
my king.
Look.
I see fire.
Keep looking.
Do you see?
Do you see. my king?
Yes.
(HORN BLOWING)
I will kill that man.
I don't care how many arrows
they feather me with.
how many spears
they run through me.
I will kill that
horn-blowing cunt
before I fall.
They want you to
know you're surrounded.
I know I'm surrounded.
I know that because
I stood on the battlements
and saw I was surrounded.
They don't want
you to sleep.
They want to sap
your spirit before...
Thank you. wise bald man.
Thank you for explaining
siege tactics to me.
No word from my father?
No.
Send more ravens.
You killed all the ravens.
The first time
I saw Winterfell...
(HORN BLOWING CONTINUES)
First time I saw Winterfell.
it looked like something
that had been here
for thousands of years
and would be here
after I was dead.
I saw it and I thought.
"Of course. Ned Stark
crushed our rebellion
and killed my brothers.
"We never stood
a chance against
the man who lives here."
Lord Stark went
out of his way to
make it your home.
Yes. my captors
were so very kind
to me.
You love reminding me
of that.
Everyone in this
frozen pile of shit
has always loved
reminding me of that.
You know what
it's like to be told
how lucky you are to
be someone's prisoner?
To be told how
much you owe them?
And then to go back home
to your real father...
(HORN BLOWING)
I will kill that man.
I swear to
the Drowned God.
the Old Gods.
the New Gods.
to every fucking god
in every fucking heaven.
I will kill that man.
Theon. listen to me.
I serve Winterfell.
Now Winterfell is yours.
I'm bound by oath
to serve you.
And what's your counsel.
trusted friend?
Run.
Five hundred Northmen
wait outside the walls.
You have 20 men.
You can't win.
Wait for nightfall and run.
There's nowhere
to run.
I'd never make it
back to the Iron Islands.
And even if I did.
even if by some miracle
I slipped through
the lines and
made it home.
I'd be a coward.
The Greyjoy who ran.
The shame of the family.
Don't go home.
Join the Night's Watch.
Once a man has
taken the black.
he's beyond
reach of the law.
All his past crimes
are forgiven.
I won't make it to the Wall.
I won't make it 10 feet
past the Winterfell gates.
There are ways.
Hidden passageways
built so the Lords of
Winterfell could escape.
The road will be dangerous.
But with a little luck...
The Night's Watch
is an ancient.
honorable order.
You'll have
opportunities there.
The opportunity for Jon Snow
to cut my throat in my sleep.
The opportunity
to make amends
for what you've done.
I've done a lot. haven't I?
Things I never
imagined myself doing.
I've known you many years.
Theon Greyjoy.
You're not the man
you're pretending to be.
Not yet.
You may be right.
But I've gone too far
to pretend to
be anything else.
(HORN BLOWING)
You hear that?
That's the mating call
of the Northmen.
They want to fuck us.
Well. I haven't had
a good fuck in weeks.
I'm ready for one.
(LAUGHING)
They say every ironborn man
is worth a dozen
from the mainland.
MAN: Aye!
You think they're right?
Aye.
We die today. brothers.
We die bleeding
from 100 wounds
with arrows in our necks
and spears in our guts.
but our war cries will
echo through eternity.
They will sing about
the battle of Winterfell
until the Iron Islands
have slipped
beneath the waves.
Every man. woman
and child will know
who we were
and how long we stood.
Aggar and Gelmarr.
Wex and Urzen.
Stygg and Black Lorren.
Ironborn warriors
will cry out our names
as they leap onto the shores
of Seagard and Faircastle.
ALL: Aye!
Mothers will name
their sons for us.
Aye!
Girls will think of us
with their lovers
inside them.
Aye!
(HORN BLOWING)
And whoever kills
that fucking horn-blower
will stand in bronze
above the shores of Pyke!
ALL: Aye!
What is dead may never die!
(SCREAMS)
Thought he'd never shut up.
It was a good speech.
Didn't want to interrupt.
What is this?
What are you doing?
(GROANS)
Let's go home.
MAN: Come on.
TYRION: Why should
I believe you?
VARYS: Why would
I lie about it?
To create strife
between my sister and me.
Where before there
was nothing but love.
Ser Mandon Moore
tried to kill you
on your sister's orders.
If it weren't for
your squire's bravery.
you'd be a dead man.
Pod.
Yes. my lord?
Would it be excessive
of me to ask you
to save my life
twice in a week?
No. my lord.
You're a good lad.
Get Bronn. tell him
I want four of
his most loyal gold cloaks
outside my door
at all times.
I'm afraid your friend
has been relieved
of his command
of the City Watch.
The gold cloaks are
now firmly in the hands
of your father or your sister.
It varies from
cloak to cloak.
Then my hill
tribesmen.
Have gone home.
Your father paid them
quite handsomely.
I'm afraid we won't
be seeing each other
for some time. my lord.
Don't want to swim too close
to a drowning man?
And I thought
we were friends.
We are.
Podrick.
would you mind?
There are many
who know that without you
this city faced
certain defeat.
The king won't
give you any honors.
the histories
won't mention you.
but we will not forget.
Come along now. Podrick.
My love.
(DOOR CLOSES)
It was good of you
to come.
Good of me?
Of course I come.
I want to see you.
Believe me. you don't.
Have you looked?
I will be the first.
(GROANS)
Well?
You are a mess.
I'm a monster as
well as a dwarf.
You should
charge me double.
You think
I'm here for money?
That was
the arrangement
we made.
I pay you
and you lie to me.
Oh.
I'm a poor little rich man
and nobody loves me.
so I make jokes all the time
and pay them to laugh.
Fuck your money.
Let's leave.
Leave?
Leave King's Landing.
They tried to kill you.
They will try again.
Going into wars.
fighting soldiers.
you're terrible at this.
Let's take a boat to Pentos
and never come back.
You don't belong here.
What would we do in Pentos?
Eat. drink.
fuck. live.
I want to go with you.
So do it.
Your father. your sister.
all these bad people.
they can't stop you.
Forget about them.
Come with me.
I can't.
I do belong here.
These bad people
are what I'm good at.
Outtalking them.
outthinking them.
It's what I am.
And I like it.
I like it more than
anything I've ever done.
Are you going to leave?
You have a shit memory.
I am yours
and you are mine.
(SNIFFLES)
(SOBBING)
SEPTON: In the sight
of the Seven.
I hereby seal
these two souls.
binding them as
one for eternity.
Look upon one another
and say the words.
Father. smith...
warrior. mother...
maiden. crone. stranger.
I am hers
and she is mine...
I am his
and he is mine...
from this day until
the end of my days.
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
Is this a riddle?
Khaleesi!
JORAH: Khaleesi!
Are you trying
to frighten me
with magic tricks?
You want me? Here I am.
Are you afraid
of a little girl?
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
HOT PIE: How did
he find us?
What are you
doing here?
Waiting for you.
How did you know
we'd come this way?
After all
the things you have seen.
this is your question?
How did you
kill those guards?
Was it hard?
No harder than
taking a new name.
if you know the way.
Show me how.
I want to be
able to do it. too.
If you would learn.
you must come with me.
Where?
Far and away across
the Narrow Sea to Braavos.
My dancing master
was from Braavos.
To be a dancing master
is a special thing.
but to be a faceless man.
that is
something else entirely.
The girl has many
names on her lips.
Joffrey.
Cersei. Tywin Lannister.
Ilyn Payne. the Hound.
Names to offer up
to the Red God.
She could offer them all
one by one.
I want to.
But I can't.
I need to find
my brother and mother.
And my sister.
I need to find her. too.
Then we must part.
A man has duties as well.
Here.
What is it?
A coin of great value.
Could it buy a horse?
It is not meant for
the buying of horses.
Then what good is it?
If the day comes
when you must find me again.
just give that coin
to any man from Braavos
and say these words to him.
"Valar Morghulis."
Valar Morghulis.
Please don't go. Jaqen.
Jaqen is dead.
Say it again.
Valar Morghulis.
Good.
Farewell. Arya Stark.
Osha.
what are you doing?
(WOLVES WHINING)
(SOBBING)
Tell us what medicine
to get from your chambers.
We'll make you better.
I feel just fine.
They burned it down.
They burned everything.
Not everything.
Not you.
But they may come back.
You have to go.
Put on your
warmest clothes.
Pack as much food
as you can carry
and go north.
North's
the wrong way.
And Mother and
brother are south.
We don't know where.
There are too many
enemies in the south.
Go to the Wall. to Jon.
He'll look after you
and let your mother
know you're safe.
I don't want to leave you.
No more than
I want to leave you.
I pulled you
into the world.
Both of you.
I've seen both your faces
almost every day since.
And for that.
I consider myself very.
very lucky.
Go now with Hodor. Go on.
I'll be right here.
Osha.
You must protect them.
You're the only one who can.
You may have to protect them
against your own kind.
I've got no great
love for my own kind.
(GASPS)
I'll get you
milk of the poppy.
Tell me where to find it.
I don't want
milk of the poppy.
Do it quickly.
(FOOTSTEPS)
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(SCREECHING CONTINUES)
(WIND BLOWING)
(SNIFFLES)
Until the sun
rises in the west
and sets in the east.
until the rivers run dry
and the mountains blow
in the wind like leaves.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
(SCREECHING CONTINUES)
They miss their mother.
They want to be with you.
Do you want to
be with them?
You will be.
When your dragons were born.
our magic was born again.
It is strongest
in their presence.
And they are
strongest in yours.
You will be with them.
through winter. summer.
winter again.
Across a thousand.
thousand seasons
you will be with them.
And we will be with you
until time comes to an end.
(DRAGONS SCREECHING)
Welcome home.
Daenerys Stormborn.
This is
not my home.
My home is across the sea.
where my people
are waiting for me.
They will be
waiting a long time.
Dracarys.
(PYAT PREE SCREAMING)
(CHAINS BREAKING)
YGRITTE: We should
be there by sundown.
Won't be a fun night
for you. Mance knows
how to make crows sing.
If you know what to say.
you might just make it
through the night.
Not talking's
not the way to go.
Careful with that.
You might cut yourself.
Never swung
a sword before. have you?
You look like
a baby with a rattle.
Enough of that!
(GRUNTS)
(SHOUTS)
(GRUNTING)
Stop!
Why. traitor?
So you can give
Mance Rayder an invitation
to Castle Black?
Let 'em fight.
(GRUNTING)
That's it?
That's what you can do?
You little shit.
Your traitor father
teach you that?
Or was it your whore mother?
(PANTING)
(GROANS)
We are
the watchers on the Wall.
You can tell Mance
that's the man who
killed Qhorin Halfhand.
Burn the body.
MAN: Aye.
You don't want this
one coming back for you.
Come along. Jon Snow.
Time to meet
the King-beyond-the-Wall.
What the...
(SCREECHES)
DOREAH: Khaleesi. please.
He said you'd never
leave Qarth alive.
DAENERYS: Come.
Nothing.
Thank you.
Xaro Xhoan Daxos.
Thank you for
teaching me this lesson.
I am king of Qarth.
I can help you now.
truly help you.
We can take the Iron Throne.
I'll bring you
a thousand ships.
Please. Khaleesi.
I beg you.
All that you have dreamed
is within your reach!
I beg you. please!
Khaleesi.
Please! Please!
XARO: Khaleesi!
(DOOR CLANKS)
It's all a lie.
Looks real enough to me.
Real enough to buy a ship?
Aye. a small ship.
(CHEERING)
(PURRING)
(SCREECHES)
(WIND HOWLING)
I thought we were
coming north to
fight wildlings.
Is this goat?
It's moose.
People shouldn't live
anywhere you need to
burn shit to keep warm.
Well. you
see a tree.
let me know.
If you step back
and think about it.
the thing about Gilly
that's so interesting is...
Just bloody kill me.
No. truly.
The thing about her
that I find
so interesting
is that after all that
Craster's done to her.
she's still got
hope that life
might get better.
The thing about Gilly
that you find
so interesting
is that she said
six words to you.
And the thing about you
that I find so interesting
is absolutely nothing.
(HORN BLOWING)
It's Jon and the Halfhand.
They're back.
(HORN BLOWS)
Two blasts
is wildlings.
You're not fighting
them alone. Come on.
(HORN BLOWING)
GRENN: Three blasts?
Run!
Wait! Wait for me!
Grenn!
Edd!
(HIGH-PITCHED WHISTLING)
(BREATHING HEAVILY)
(SOBBING)
(SHRIEKING)
Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today